

ATASHA POTTER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

FAIRFAX, VA MS.APOTTER@GMAIL.COM

SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN:

WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ATASHAPOTTER/

GITHUB:

MSAPOTTER.GITHUB.IO/

PROFILE

Software engineer with 10+ years of analytical experience. My civilian career and military history reflect a dedicated work ethic, attention to detail, and desire for continuous learning. Originally from Hawaii, I have a laid back, island disposition and multicultural worldview.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER STUDENT

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | MAR 2019 - JUN 2019

- Completing a 3-month, 500-hour, full-time and full-stack software engineer/web development program covering the latest front and back-end languages and frameworks.
- Program utilizes a hands-on approach, following KISS and DRY best practices, and adhering to the GitHub fork and pull request model for collaboration.
- Project #1: Classic Hangman game with a Game of Thrones spin. Tech stack: vanilla JS | HTML | CSS
- Pre-class Project: Classic Rock Paper Scissors game with a Big Bang Theory twist. Tech stack: vanilla Javascript | HTML | CSS
- Pre-class Project: Simple memory game. Tech stack: vanilla Javascript | HTML | CSS

INTELLIGENCE ANALYST

LEIDOS/ BAE SYSTEMS/OAK GROVE | MAY 2011 - MAR 2019

- Performed data mining of classified and open source information; and created summaries of intelligence analysis to make recommendations based on that data
- Given product parameters, worked individually to produce analysis summaries which was merged with a bigger product

EXECUTIVE OFFICER | INTELLIGENCE ANALYST

UNITED STATES ARMY

| JAN 2004 - MAR 2009

 Performed data mining of classified and open source information; and created summaries of intelligence analysis

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE PROGRAM

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | 2019

CYBERSECURITY PROGRAM

NEW HORIZONS LEARNING CENTER | 2017

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE. AEROSPACE ENGINEERING

UNIVERSITY OF NOTRE DAME | 1999-2003

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- MongoDB
- Express
- Node

- React
- Python
- Django
- AJAX

APIs

- JSON
- Git Github
- - Command Line
 - REST

Mongoose

Bootstrap